dataplugs.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy policy | Long-term relationships with our customers | DataPlugs

## Privacy

Our mission is to build long-term relationships with our customers based on trust. Dataplugs will do everything in its power to ensure that your right to privacy is maintained and protected. Our Services are not directed to children under the age of 18 years old.

## Information We Collect and Why?

  * First & last name or company name
  * Postal address
  * Telephone and fax numbers
  * URL
  * E-mail address
  * Credit card information
  * Other billing information

Dataplugs may also collect information on how users access our Services using a tracking ID unique to each user through the use of cookies or other similar means.

## What are Cookies?

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For session ID cookies, once you close your browser or log out, the cookie terminates and is erased. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on your computer’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Your browser’s help file contains information and instructions for removing persistent cookies. Session ID cookies may be used by Dataplugs to track user preferences while the user is using our Services. They also help to minimize load times and save on server processing. Persistent cookies may be used by Dataplugs to store whether, for example, you want your password remembered or not, and other information. Cookies used on Dataplugs websites do not contain personally identifiable information.

## What is Log Files?

Like most standard websites, we use log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. However, none of the information stored in our log files, including but not limited to IP addresses, is linked to personally identifiable information.

## How we use the information we collect?

Dataplugs may from time to time engage third parties, including but not limited to, its own subsidiaries, affiliate companies, and business partners to preserve, analyze, store or manipulate information collected from Users on behalf of Dataplugs in connection with delivering Dataplugs services. In all such cases, such third party service providers or business partners will be required to treat all such information collected from Users, including Users personally identifiable data, with the same degree of care as Dataplugs and they will be prohibited from disclosing such data to any other person or party, except as otherwise provided for in this Privacy Policy.

We may also use this information for research purposes regarding the effectiveness of our Services and marketing and sales efforts. Dataplugs will not in any way share this information with a third party either for free or by selling it, unless you specifically authorize such disclosures.

## Disclosure of Information

Dataplugs may also disclose aggregate, anonymous, data based on information collected from users to investors and potential partners. In such cases, statistical information will be disclosed and personally identifiable data will be kept strictly confidential. In case Dataplugs is sold, the information collected from users may be transferred to the new owners.

Dataplugs may from time to time engage third parties, including its own subsidiaries and affiliated companies, to preserve, analyze or otherwise store or manipulate data received by Dataplugs from its customers. In all such cases, such third party service providers will be required to treat all such data with the same degree of care as Dataplugs and they will be prohibited from disclosing such data to any other person or party, except as otherwise provided for in this Privacy Policy.

## Special Offers and Updates

Our customers and users will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and possibly a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications.

## Service Announcements

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement, if, for instance, our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.

## Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law, if we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary and required to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on Dataplugs.

Dataplugs websites contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Dataplugs is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. The Dataplugs Privacy Policy as described herein applies solely to information collected by Dataplugs.

## Maintenance of Information

The information provided to Dataplugs is saved indefinitely and may be stored on one or more databases directly or indirectly maintained by Dataplugs. Dataplugs employs industry standard security measures to protect the confidentiality of the information.

While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration to data will not occur; we make every effort to prevent such occurrences. Any other particularly sensitive information, such as credit card numbers collected for commercial transactions, is encrypted prior to transmission by you to Dataplugs.

## Your Responsibility

You are responsible for the security of the login information, such as usernames and passwords, which give you access to your private information maintained by Dataplugs. Make sure you keep login information in a safe place and do not share it with others.

Note that key-loggers, viruses, or other surveillance devices can intercept login information on the computers from which you access our Services, so you should take precautions regarding such devices, especially from public computers. In addition, you should always log out from any relevant Services when you are not actively using them.

## Questions

If you have any questions concerning this Privacy Policy please contact us at [cs@dataplugs.com](mailto:cs@dataplugs.com)
